Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- 10: Records
  - Coping With the Gypsy Moth, 1982/02; cuid1894; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Correspondence, 1968; cuid1895; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979; cuid1896; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989; cuid1897; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 278)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 278)
  - Correspondence, undated; cuid1898; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Correspondence and Proposals, 1980-1986; cuid1899 (Box 191)
  - Correspondence Course Annual Reports, undated; cuid1900; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Correspondence Courses in Agriculture, Family Living, and Community Development, undated; cuid1901; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - County Associations Constitutions and Bylaws, undated; cuid1902; 1 Items (Box 143)
  - County Commissioners' Symposium, 1980/05; cuid1903; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - County Extension Agents Annual Reports, 1957-1959; cuid1904 (Box 185)
  - County Staff Time Distribution, 1953-1964; cuid1905; 1 Items (Box 152)
  - Creating an Organizational Environment to Support a Balanced Personal and Professional Life, 2000 (Box 277)
  - Creating a Workplace that Supports Balanced Personal and Professional Lives Task Force, 2000 (Box 280)
  - Creative Career Exploration Program, undated; cuid1906; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Crop Management Associations, 1985/04; cuid1907; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Crop Management Extension Group (CMEG), 2008; cuid2417 (Box 236)
  - CUPRAP Professional Development Conference Planning, 2008-2013; cuid2460 (Box 241)
  - Curing and Smoking Poultry Products, undated; cuid1908; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Custom Pack Series, undated; cuid1909; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Ag Extension Guide
  - Customize Your Diet for an In-look, undated; cuid1910; 1 Items (Box 178)
    4-H Information Guide
  - Dairy Cattle Breeding Short Course, 1964/03; cuid1911; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Dairy Herd Management Conference, 1970/02; cuid1912; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Dairy Management Workshop for Youth, 1988/10; cuid1913; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Dairy Manufacturing Short Courses, 1967-1968; cuid1914; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Data on Pennsylvania Farms, 1967/09; cuid1915; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Day Camp, 1977; cuid1916 (Box 185)
  - Day Camp, 1979-1985; cuid1917 (Box 185)
  - Dedication of the William L. Henning Building, 1983/04; cuid1918; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Dept. of Horticulture Guide to Majors and Minors, undated; cuid1919; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Design Applications of Mechanical Properties of Solid Food Materials Workshop, 1975/08; cuid1920; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Design With Color, undated; cuid1921; 1 Items (Box 178)
    4-H Member's Guide
  - Designing a Sanitation Program for the Food Industry - Food Science Dept., 1987/10; cuid1922; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Development Guidelines for Extension Plans of Work, 1990 (Box 279)
  - Deveopment Guidelines for Plans of Work, 1996-1999 (Box 280)
  - Developing Cooperative Extension Educational Initiatives, 1989-1990 (Box 277)
  - Developing Effective Programs for Hard-to-Reach Audiences, undated; cuid1923; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - DHIA Records: Put More Money in Your Milk Pail, undated; cuid1924; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Diffusion Process/Group Process/Effective Meetings/Guideposts for Better Meetings/Meeting Aids, undated; cuid1925; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass
  - Directions for Completing County Extension - Director Administrative Review, 1993; cuid1926; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Diseases of Ornamental and Shade Trees, Shrubs, Vines, and Ground Covers, undated; cuid1927; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Diversity of the American Community, 1967/12; cuid1928; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Do You Know Your EBDCs?, undated; cuid1929; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Don't Forget!, undated; cuid1930; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Cooperative Extension Info Sheet
  - Dozen Ways to Strengthen Your Family, undated; cuid1931; 1 Items; Textual--Leaflets (Box 179)
  - Draft, undated; cuid1932; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Dunlap Thesis (Cornell University), undated; cuid1933; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Eastern Apicultural Society, 1968/08; cuid1934; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Economic Stress in Central Pennsylvania, undated; cuid1935; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Educational Programs, 1996-1999; cuid1936; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Educational Programs for Future, undated; cuid1937; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Slide Shows (Box 162)
  - Educational Programs, Plans of Work, 1992-1999 (Box 279)
  - Effective Teaching in Agriculture: By All Means - 23rd National Conference, 1977/06; cuid1938; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - EFNEP, 2003-2008; cuid2416 (Box 236)
  - EFNEP (Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program) Food Stamp Project Study Field Work, 1982-1984; cuid1939; 1 Items (Box 132)
  - EFNEP Calendars, 1990; cuid1940 (Box 177)
  - EFNEP Calendars, 1981-1988; cuid1941; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - EFNEP Homemaker Questionnaires by County, undated; cuid1942; 1 Items (Box 137)
  - EFNEP Printouts, Samples, Data and Synopsis, undated; cuid1943; 1 Items (Box 137)
  - EMIS Data Definitions, undated; cuid1944; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Employee Distribution by County Unit, undated; cuid1945; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Energy Guide Label for a Refrigerator-Freezer, undated; cuid1946; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Enjoy Eating Vegetables - Food for Health, undated; cuid1947; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Environmental Resource Management, undated; cuid1948; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Erie County Field Research Laboratory - Northeast, Pennsylvania, undated; cuid1949; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Establishment of Forage Crops By Conservation - Tillage - Pest Management, 1986/06; cuid1950; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Evaluations and Reviews, undated; cuid1951; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Evening Classes, 1927-1972; cuid1952; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Examination for Certification of Private Applicator, undated; cuid1953; 1 Items (Box 177)
    Dept. of Ag Letter
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program, undated; cuid1954; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program Annual Action Plan and State Plans of Work, 1996-1999 (Box 279)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program Annual Action Plans, 1997 (Box 279)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program Annual Work Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 280)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program Annual Work Plan, 1995 (Box 279)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program Banquet, 1978/06; cuid1955; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program Plan of Work, 1992-1995 (Box 279)
  - Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program State Plans of Work and Annual Action Plans, 1996-1999 (Box 280)
  - Establishing Educational Priorities, 1994 (Box 280)
  - Expanded Nutrition Education Program, undated; cuid1956; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Extension Activities Summary Binder, 1922-1946; cuid1957; 1 Items (Box 152)
  - Extension Annual Report, 2007-2008 (Box 278)
  - Extension Annual Report, 2009-2010 (Box 278)
  - Extension Bulletin Volume 1-5, undated; cuid1958; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Extension Education Seminars, undated; cuid1959; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - Extension Extended, 1991-2016 (Box 262)
  - Extension In 80's Survey, undated; cuid1960; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Extension Leadership Team - CED Issues, 2000 (Box 277)
  - Extension Memories, 2005-2008 (Box 277)
  - Extension Service Annual Reports, 1912-1962; cuid1961; 1 Items (Box 105)
  - Extension Service at Penn State Plans of Work for, 1929-1938; cuid1962; 1 Items (Box 111)
  - Extension Service at Penn State Plans of Work for, 1939-1945; cuid1963; 1 Items (Box 112)
  - Extension Service at Penn State Plans of Work for, 1946-1955; cuid1964; 1 Items (Box 113)
  - Extension Service at Penn State Plans of Work for, 1956-1963; cuid1965; 1 Items (Box 114)
  - Extension Service at Penn State Plans of Work for, 1962-1972; cuid1966; 1 Items (Box 131)
  - Extension Specialist Narrative Reports, 1955-1957; cuid1967; 1 Items (Box 116)
  - Extension Staffing Models, 2002-2004; cuid2459 (Box 240)
  - Extension Summary Reports Bound Volumes, 1933-1945; cuid1968; 1 Items (Box 152)
  - Extension Summary Reports Bound Volumes, 1948-1956; cuid1969; 1 Items (Box 152)
  - Extension: What is it?, undated; cuid1970; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Extra-Mural Courses, 1924-1938; cuid1971; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Facts About…Agricultural Engineering, undated; cuid1972; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Facts About…Agricultural Mechanization, undated; cuid1973; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Faculty Staff Survey, 2008 (Box 278)
  - Fallout Protection for Dairy Cattle, undated; cuid1974; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Family Living Outlook, undated; cuid1975; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Farm Contact Charts and Data, undated; cuid1976; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Farm Equipment Conference, 1961/01; cuid1977; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Farm Income Tax and Social Security Short Course, 1968/12; cuid1978; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Farm Management in Regions, 1994-1997; cuid1979 (Box 191)
  - Fat Child Can Become a Fat Adult, undated; cuid1980; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Father, Will Your Son Stay on the Farm?, undated; cuid1981; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Federal and State Income Tax Workshop for Practitioners, 1977; cuid1982; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Federal Legislation, undated; cuid1983; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Federal Revenues in Small Communities, 1979/10; cuid1984; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Feed Quality Control Conference, 1971/03; cuid1985; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Financial Budgets, 1917-1950; cuid1986; 1 Items (Box 105)
  - Financial Budgets, 1942-1949; cuid1987; 1 Items (Box 106)
  - Financial Reports, 1917-1950; cuid1988; 1 Items (Box 105)
  - Finishing Touch: Design for Frames and Mats, undated; cuid1989; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Fire Safety Education, undated; cuid1990; 1 Items (Box 178)
    4-H Project Guides #1,3
  - First Annual Reports, undated; cuid1991; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Flammable Fabrics and the Elderly - U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission, undated; cuid1992; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Florist Facts, undated; cuid1993; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Florist Facts - Energy Management in the Production of Greenhouse Crops, undated; cuid1994; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Focus on Leadership, undated; cuid1995; 1 Items (Box 178)
    4-H Leaders' Education Course Sheets
  - Follow the Food Guide Everyday, undated; cuid1996; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Food and Cooking Guide, undated; cuid1997; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Food and Nutrition Progression Record, undated; cuid1998; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Food Industry Waste Management Conference Emphasizing Problem-Solving Methods and Least-Cost Alternatives, 1969/05; cuid1999; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Food Sanitation Series, undated; cuid2000; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Foods and Nutrition Extension
  - Food Stamp Data, Printouts, Tapes, Documentation and Slides, undated; cuid2001; 1 Items (Box 118)
  - Food Stamp Project Study, 1980-1983; cuid2002; 1 Items (Box 118)
  - Food Use Sheet - Background Information, undated; cuid2003; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Forage Crop Program, undated; cuid2004; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Forage Workshop, 1971/03; cuid2005; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - 4-H Creating Comm Unity Networks, 2009 (Box 278)
  - Four Major Food Groups, undated; cuid2006; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Fruit Research Lab at Biglerville: History and Accomplishments, 1918-1976; cuid2007; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - FUMO Grants, 2005; cuid2440 (Box 239)
  - Funsheets (#1-10), undated; cuid2008; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Ag Extension Sheets
  - Future of Pennsylvania Agriculture and Rural Community, 1987/03; cuid2009; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Garden Institute - Retailing Conference for Owners, Managers, Retail Sales Personnel of Independently-Owned Garden Centers in the Eastern States, 1965/07; cuid2010; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Getting to Know Your Community - Project 1, undated; cuid2011; 1 Items (Box 178)
    4-H Member Guide
  - Goals and Highlights, 1999; cuid2012; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Goals and Program Highlights, 1998; cuid2013; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Goals and Program Highlights, 1996-1997; cuid2014; 2 Items (Box 175)
  - Goals and Program Highlights, 1996-1998 (Box 278)
  - Goals and Program Highlights, 1997-1998; cuid2015; 2 Items (Box 176)
  - Goals and Program Highlights, 1999 (Box 280)
  - Government Performance and Results Act - Performance Plans, 1998-2001; cuid2016; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - GPRA Performance Plan Annual Report, 1998-2001 (Box 280)
  - GPRA Performance Plans, 1998-2001 (Box 280)
  - Graduate Programs in the College of Agriculture at Penn State, undated; cuid2017; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Graduate Studies and Research in Entomology, undated; cuid2018; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Graduate Studies in Entomology, undated; cuid2019; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 178)
  - Graduate Studies in Forest Resources, undated; cuid2020; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Graduate Study in Animal Science, undated; cuid2021; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Greenhouse Easter Lily Production Pointers, undated; cuid2022; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Greenhouse Easter Lily Production Pointers, undated; cuid2023; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Gregory Gonk Cooperative Extension Series, undated; cuid2024; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Growing with America - The Pennsylvania Nurserymen's Association Roster, 1970; cuid2025; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Grow - Healthy Children and Families Impact Report, 2005 (Box 277)
  - Hallett, George Land Grant Universities Speech, 1945; cuid2026; 1 Items (Box 153)
  - Handbook of Guidelines for Planning, Conducting, and Evaluating Group Meetings - Volumes I and II, undated; cuid2027; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Hardwood Lumber Grading and Inspection Workshop, 1977/02; cuid2028; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Health and Safety in the Arts and Crafts, undated; cuid2029; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Health Trustees Leadership Program, undated; cuid2030; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Health Trustees Leadership Program, undated; cuid2031; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Health-Related Programs and Resources - Pennsylvania Cooperative Extension Service, undated; cuid2032; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Helping - the 5th H, undated; cuid2033; 1 Items (Box 178)
    4-H Participant's Manual
  - Here's What Your County Extension Office Can Do For You, undated; cuid2034; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Heritage We Share, 1979/10/31; cuid2035 (Box 166)
  - High Lime-Liquid Fertilizer Program for Corn, undated; cuid2036; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Hints for Family Fitness, undated; cuid2037; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Hints on Measuring, undated; cuid2038; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Historical Appraisal of Development of County Extension Agents in Pennsylvania, undated; cuid2039; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Historical Material, undated; cuid2040; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Historical Material, undated; cuid2041; 1 Items (Box 143)
  - Historical Material, undated; cuid2042; 1 Items (Box 155)
  - Home Economics Extension: A Service for You, undated; cuid2043; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Honor Society of Agriculture, Gamma Sigma Delta, Initiation Banquet, 1989/04; cuid2044; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Horse Judging Clinic, 1972/04; cuid2045; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Horseback Riding for the Handicapped, undated; cuid2046; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - How Can We In Extension Improve the Environment? - Cooperative Extension Service, undated; cuid2047; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - How to Use the Penn State Forage Testing Service, undated; cuid2048; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Implementation of Flow Chart, undated; cuid2049; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - In Honor of Milton W. DeLancey, undated; cuid2050; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - In Memory of Herman R. Purdy, 1985/10; cuid2051; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Increase Your Farm Income Through Linear Programming, undated; cuid2052; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Indoor Gardening, undated; cuid2053; 1 Items (Box 177)
    4-H Plant Science Leader's Guide
  - Info on Vitamins and Nutrition, undated; cuid2054; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Ag and Human Development Series Info Sheets
  - Information for Sewage Sludge and Diagnostic Soil Tests, 1980, 1984; cuid2055; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Instructions for Taking Samples for Plant Analysis, undated; cuid2056; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - International Conference on Ecology and Population Management of Black Flies, 1985/05; cuid2057; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - International Farm Youth Exchange, undated; cuid2058; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - International Symposium on Ecology and Revegetation of Drastically Disturbed Areas, 1969/08; cuid2059; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Interpreting Soil Tests for Agronomic Crops, undated; cuid2060; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Interpreting Soil Tests for Horticultural Crops and Potatoes, undated; cuid2061; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Interpreting Soil Tests for Turfgrass Establishment, undated; cuid2062; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Interpreting Soil Tests for Turfgrass Maintenance, undated; cuid2063; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Interviewer's Household Identification List and Accident/Illness Record by Farm, undated; cuid2064; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Jug Dairy Processor Conference, 1977/02; cuid2065; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Keep Disease Out, Protect Pig Profits, Make More Money, undated; cuid2066; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Keys to Farm Financial Success: Survive the 80s, Reduce Financial Stress, Make Sound Decisions, and Know Your Cash Flow, undated; cuid2067; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Keystone 21: Embracing new partners and passion for food systems education, undated (Box 277)
  - Keystone Shepherds' Symposium, 1986/12; cuid2068; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Kipp: Farmer's Week at Penn State Photos, undated; cuid2069; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints (Box 172)
    Rolled
  - Kipp: List of Photographs, undated; cuid2070; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Kipp: Negatives, undated; cuid2071; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - Kipp: Photographs, undated; cuid2072; 4 Items (Box 172)
  - Kipp: Photographs & Negatives, undated; cuid2073; 1 Items (Box 172)
  - La Extension Del Programa de Educativo Alimentos y Nutricion, undated; cuid2074; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Learning to Manage America's Tomorrow, undated; cuid2075; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Let Color Work for You: Using Your Best Colors to Your Advantage, undated; cuid2076; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Let's Preserve Sweet Corn, 1987-1988; cuid2077; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Link Up With Technology - Extension Technology Conference, 1991; cuid2078; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Local Delivery Route Management Workshop, 1973; cuid2079; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Local Tax Forums, Partnership with CCAP, 2008; cuid2434 (Box 237)
  - Lumber Drying Workshop, 1967/10; cuid2080; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Lunch and Learn Series, undated; cuid2081; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Major in Poultry Technology and Management at Penn State, undated; cuid2082; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Majors in the College of Agriculture, undated; cuid2083; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Majors in the College of Agriculture - Ag Economics, Rural Sociology, Ag Business Management, undated; cuid2084; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Majors in the Dept. of Dairy and Animal Science at Penn State University, undated; cuid2085; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Majors in the School of Forest Resources in the College of Agriculture at Penn State, undated; cuid2086; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Managing for Success - Business Management Training Programs for Food Industries in PA, undated; cuid2087; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Managing Your Money - A Family Plan, undated; cuid2088; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - March: National Nutrition Month - Hints for Fitness and Health, undated; cuid2089; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Marketing Pennsylvania-Grown Christmas Trees, 1987/11; cuid2090; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Master Farmers Directory, 1927-1984; cuid2091; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Master Gardener Program Report, 2000 (Box 277)
  - Master Gardener Program Report, 2002 (Box 280)
  - Master Gardener Program Report, 2002-2004 (Box 277)
  - Master Gardeners, 2000-2008; cuid2414 (Box 236)
  - Mastitis, Milk and Money Program - A Program for Dairymen in Central PA, undated; cuid2092; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - McDowell Lecture Series, 1985-2004; cuid2619 (Box 200)
    General
    The bulk of this dates from 1985 - 1996.
  - Meal Planning: Get Off to a Smart Start, undated; cuid2093; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Meetings, 2006; cuid2442 (Box 239)
  - MG Sustainability Report and State Coordinator Position Background Information, 2004-2005; cuid2413 (Box 235)
  - Middle Atlantic Lecturers' Conference and Pennsylvania State Grange Leadership School, 1965; cuid2094; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Milkers' School, 1975; cuid2095; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, 1936-1942; cuid2096; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass Lantern
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, 1936-1942; cuid2097; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass Lantern
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, 1936-1942; cuid2098; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass Lantern
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, 1936-1942; cuid2099; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass Lantern
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, 1936-1942; cuid2100; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass Lantern
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, undated; cuid2101; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, undated; cuid2102; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass
  - Miscellaneous Agriculture and Home Economics Extension, undated; cuid2103; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--35mm
  - Moth Flies in the Home, undated; cuid2104; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Mr. Dairyman: Keeping Pesticides Out of Milk, undated; cuid2105; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - NACAA Teamwork - 82nd Annual Meeting and Conference, 35624; cuid2106; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - National Association County Agricultural Agents Annual Meeting, 1983; cuid2107 (Box 191)
  - National Association County Agricultural Agents Annual Meeting, 1985; cuid2108 (Box 191)
  - National Hampshire Sheep Type Conference, 1971/04; cuid2109; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - National Workshop - State and Federal Liaison, 1984/12; cuid2110; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - NDHIA Inc. Sixth Annual Meeting, 1971/03; cuid2111; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Need Help Stretching Your Food Budget? - Ask EFNEP, undated; cuid2112; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Needs Assessment, 1993 (Box 279)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation, 1968; cuid2113; 1 Items (Box 136)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation, 1965-1966; cuid2114; 1 Items (Box 141)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation, 1966-1967; cuid2115; 1 Items (Box 140)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation Administration, undated; cuid2116; 1 Items (Box 128)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation Evaluations, 1970; cuid2117; 1 Items (Box 125)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corporation Evaluations, 1970; cuid2118; 1 Items (Box 125)